<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Gold Ring Of Russa</string>
    <string name="btn_smallRing" translatable="false">Small Gold Ring</string>
    <string name="btn_bigRing" translatable="false">Big Gold Ring</string>
    <string name="btn_info" translatable="false">Informatin</string>
    <string name="tv_bigGoldRing" translatable="false">Along with the classic \"eight-point\"
        golden route, there are also more extended ones — their composition depends only on the
        imagination of tour operators. By the way, many additional cities are no worse than the
        main ones, that is, they are just as wonderful in terms of landscapes, culture and
        traditions.  I have already listed an approximate list of additional cities,
        so I don\'t see the point in duplicating it here. Personally, I would advise
        you to at least visit.</string>
    <string name="tv_bogolubovo" translatable="false">Bogolyubovo - here the Holy Bogolyubsky
        Convent and the very picturesque Church of the Intercession on the Nerl
        are worthy of attention. Golden Ring - Bogolyubovo</string>
    <string name="tv_info" translatable="false">The most convenient way to see the Golden Ring,
        especially if you do not live in Moscow, is, of course, an organized tour in which you
        will be brought—taken away, fed, settled and told. Its only drawback is the \"gallop
        across Europe\". Such tours last on average from 2 to 5 days, but there are also 7 and
        10 day routes.  Quite often, the starting point for traveling along the Golden Ring is
        the city of Sergiev Posad, located about 54 km north of Moscow (from the MKAD) and is
        its closest point to the Mother See. The most remote point in this group of routes is
        Kostroma, located 340 km from the capital.  There are many tour operators on the tourist
        market offering similar tours, but the prices are all about the same, the minimum cost of
        such a trip starts from 3,990 rubles for 2 days with breakfast, and reaches about 22,490
        rubles for a 7-day trip with three meals a day.  Of course, it\'s up to you to decide
        whether it\'s a lot or a little, but if you live in Moscow or the region and have a car
        plus a good guidebook, then it\'s probably easier to go along these routes yourself,
        having previously compiled a detailed itinerary of the trip so as not to miss anything
        and understand about the cost of visiting and opening hours of the most important
        attractions.  You can\'t get on a train along the Golden Ring, because the railway
        connects mainly only regional centers, such as Yaroslavl or Vladimir, and in many small
        points the stations are often located at a considerable distance from tourist places,
        which is quite inconvenient.  Special thanks to the creator of this guidebook Author:
        Andrey Petrenko  https://tourweek.ru/articles/world/277593</string>
    <string name="tv_goldRingOfRussia" translatable="false">The Golden Ring, known among foreigners
        as the Golden Ring of Russia— is a group of popular tourist routes passing through ancient
        Russian cities located on the territories of 6 Central European regions: Moscow, Vladimir,
        Ivanovo, Kostroma, as well as Tver and Yaroslavl.  The so-called classic Golden Ring is a
        route of eight points - Vladimir, Ivanovo, Kostroma, Pereslavl-Zalessky, Rostov, Sergiev
        Posad, Suzdal and Yaroslavl. That is, these are the main cities of the Golden Ring of
        Russia. In addition, often when tour operators make sightseeing trips along the Golden
        Ring, other equally interesting places are included in the routes: Alexandrov, Bogolyubovo,
        Gorokhovets, Gus-Khrustalny, Dmitrov, Kalyazin, Kideksha, Martynovo, Murom, Myshkin, Palekh,
        Ples, Rybinsk, Tutaev, Uglich, as well as Yuryev-Polsky, Shuya and others. That is,
        these are additional cities of the Golden Ring of Russia.  In April 2016, the city of
        Kaluga was officially included among the cities of the Golden Ring of Russia.  The main
        thing that unites the first and second lists is that all these cities have unique
        architectural, historical or cultural attractions that reveal the diversity and richness
        of Russian folk traditions.</string>
    <string name="tv_ivanovo" translatable="false">Tourists usually come to the bride city of
        Ivanovo with a small sightseeing tour, during which they inspect the historical center,
        where former merchant houses of the 19th and 20th centuries have been preserved, as well
        as monuments of constructivism (the 30s of the last century of the XX century), including
        the Ship House. It is also possible to note the oldest civil brick building of the city -
        the Shchudrov tent (17th century) and the Holy Vvedensky Convent.</string>
    <string name="tv_kalyzin" translatable="false">Kalyazin - the hallmark of this town is the
        Trinity-Makaryev monastery complex, flooded during the creation of the Uglich reservoir,
        with a 60-meter bell tower \"floating\" on a small island.</string>
    <string name="tv_kideksha" translatable="false">Kideksha is located near Suzdal, and is famous,
        first of all, for its white stone church of Boris and Gleb, included in the UNESCO
        heritage list. This church was built in the 12th century and is considered the first white
        stone building in the whole of northeastern Russia.</string>
    <string name="tv_costroma" translatable="false">Kostroma is interesting, first of all, for
        its historical center with a historical layout structure approved by Catherine II, which
        is based on a radial grid of streets. The main city square is Susaninskaya, with beautiful
        historical buildings, such as a Fire tower, a former guardhouse building, and Shopping
        malls occupying a fairly large territory. And, of course, the highlight of the Kostroma
        program is the Ipatievsky Monastery.</string>
    <string name="tv_miskino" translatable="false">In Myshkin, you can see with your own eyes the
        exhibits of the only Mouse Museum in the world, as well as visit the Russian Valenki
        Museum and a rather interesting historical and ethnographic open-air museum with
        traditional folk buildings. Also, tourists usually visit the Assumption Cathedral and
        stroll along the boulevard, where a beautiful wooden building has been preserved.</string>
    <string name="tv_pereslavl" translatable="false">In Pereslavl-Zalessky you can see the Red
        Square, several interesting monastery complexes and churches, including the Transfiguration
        Cathedral, as well as the Peter the Great Boat Estate Museum, the Steam Locomotive
        Museum and the Iron Museum. By the way, it is believed that it was in this cathedral
        that many Pereslavl princes were baptized, among whom was Alexander Nevsky.</string>
    <string name="tv_ples" translatable="false">Russian Russian province, the beautiful town
        of Ples, comfortably located on the high bank of the Volga, was founded in 1410 and was
        praised by the brush of Levitan himself as a mirror of the Russian province and the key
        to understanding such a mysterious Russian soul.</string>
    <string name="tv_rostov" translatable="false">In Rostov the Great, travelers usually visit
        the Rostov Kremlin Museum-Reserve, as well as beautiful monasteries, including the
        Spaso-Yakovlevsky and Avraamiev Bogoyavlensky. The wooden and stone buildings of the city
        (XVIII-XX centuries) are also of great historical value.</string>
    <string name="tv_sergeev_passad" translatable="false">Sergiev Posad is known for its
        Trinity-Sergius Lavra, which is considered the largest Orthodox monastery in our country.
        It is under UNESCO protection. Its numerous architectural structures were built by the best
        architects of the XV-XIX centuries. There are more than 50 buildings of various purposes
        in the ensemble of the monastery. By the way, this is where one of the episodes of \"Ivan
        Vasilyevich changing his profession\" takes place. In addition, there is a wonderful Toy
        Museum in the city, founded back in 1918.</string>
    <string name="tv_suzdal" translatable="false">Suzdal is, first of all, the famous Suzdal
        Kremlin, which is the oldest part of the city (the beginning of the 11th century).
        The Kremlin has preserved to this day the earthen ramparts and moats of the ancient
        fortress, as well as three churches, a complex of bishops\' chambers and the Nativity
        Cathedral. In addition, there are five wonderful monastery complexes in Suzdal:
        Spaso-Evfimiev, Pokrovsky, Alexandrovsky, Rizopolozhensky and Vasilievsky. There are
        also many old churches, old Shopping malls and a wonderful Museum of
        Wooden Architecture.</string>
    <string name="tv_tuev" translatable="false">\"Pearl on the Volga\" – the city of Tutaev
        is named. Its churches are picturesquely scattered along the hilly banks of the Mother
        Volga, and it is the local landscape that attracts the attention of tourists
        coming here.</string>
    <string name="tv_uglich" translatable="false">Uglich is famous for its historical center,
        where its main attractions are located - the Uglich Kremlin, the ancient Church of Dmitry
        on Blood (1692) and the Transfiguration Cathedral. In addition, there are three monasteries
        in the city – Resurrection, Epiphany and Alekseevsky. Also of interest are the civil
        buildings (merchant estates) and the ensemble of the Shopping Area with
        Shopping malls.</string>
    <string name="tv_vladimir" translatable="false">Vladimir, whose main attractions are the Golden
        Gate fortress, the white-stone Assumption and Dmitrievsky cathedrals and several beautiful
        churches of the XVII-XVIII centuries. The Water Tower also deserves attention. By the way,
        it is in Vladimir that the high–security prison, Vladimir Central, sung by Mikhail Krug,
        is located.</string>
    <string name="tv_yaroslavl" translatable="false">In Yaroslavl, considered the oldest city on
        the Volga (1010), tourists can see an outstanding example of Catherine II\'s urban planning
        policy – the historical center of the city, as well as the Transfiguration Monastery and
        the beautiful Church of Elijah the Prophet.</string>
    <string name="rb_eng">ENG</string>
    <string name="rb_ru">RU</string>
    <string name="rb_rus">rb_rus</string>
</resources>